pcgameweb.com 2001-12-01

# GamerWeb.com: Superior Games Coverage

**GAMERWEB.COM PRIVACY POLICY**

**General Information**  
At GamerWeb.com we respect the privacy of our users. For that reason, we follow a strict privacy policy. Here you will find details on this policy. 

GamerWeb.com limited ("GamerWeb.com") provides online information and services related to gaming and any other issues deemed by GamerWeb.com to be of interest to its audience. The term "GamerWeb.com" means any and all pages located on the main site (http://www.gamerweb.com") and GamerWeb's hubsites ("GamerWeb.com Hubsites"). GamerWeb.com Hubsites are identified as the websites listed under GamerWeb.com Hubsites, and are limited these listed sites only. If a website is not accessible via the main page at GamerWeb.com, and is not listed on this page under GamerWeb.com Hubsites, then it is not a GamerWeb.com hubsite and it is not associated with GamerWeb.com. 

**Standard User Data**  
The standard data we collect about our users is not personally identifiable information. This means it is not information which identifies them as an individual. By any of using GamerWeb.com's services or reading its content, you agree that you understand the nature this data collection. 

When you log onto GamerWeb.com, certain standard information is normally collected by our servers. This information may include, but may not be limited to, the location or website from which you came; the time you spend on parts of GamerWeb.com or its related sites; the operating system you use on your computer (for example, Microsoft Windows 98); the software you use to browse the Internet (for example Microsoft Internet Explorer); the amount of information you access from GamerWeb.com; your geographical location (specific only to country and/or state); the account from which you are accessing the Internet and subsequently GamerWeb.com; and your IP address. Your IP address is a number designated by your Internet Service Provider that identifies the account you are using to access the Internet with your Internet Service Provider, and/or the Internet Service Provider you are using to access the Internet itself. This data collection is standard and common to most websites on the Internet. 

This information does not identify you as an individual, and none of this information will be disclosed in any form that is specific to you as a user of GamerWeb.com, unless otherwise stated. For example, an area of GamerWeb.com exempt from this practise is the forum, which display your IP address as a means of tracking your use of the forums. GamerWeb.com will not otherwise knowingly retain and/or disclose this standard data other than in an aggregate forms, including, but not limited to, demographic data averages, which GamerWeb may use to improve its services. 

**Personal User Data**  
The only ways in which GamerWeb may receive personally identifiable information about you is if you knowingly and willingly provide the information through of our service areas, including, but not limited to, contests and promotions. In such areas, the information you disclose is done so knowingly and willingly, at your sole discretion. The personally identifiable information you disclose is optional, and is normally required so as to effectively enter you into a contest we may offer. 

We may, from time to time, collect data on our users. Users may provide personally identifiable information, knowingly and of their own accord. This information is provided at the user's discretion. This personally identifiable information will be destroyed after a period of one (1) year, or when it is no longer required, in accordance with the Data Protection Act, 1984. GamerWeb.com may share the aggregate results of the data it receives, with advertisers and partners to help them better understand our services and their opportunities, although we will not disclose personal data. 

**Advertising**  
GamerWeb.com works with a third party that serves ads to this site. To find out more about how Flycast manages the privacy of information in conjunction with serving ads on this site, please go to http://www.flycast.com/about_us/about-privacy.html. 

**Protection**  
No computer system is one hundred per cent protected, and although the means through which data is submitted to GamerWeb.com are safe, we cannot guarantee that data will not unlawfully be retrieved by third parties. When data is submitted to GamerWeb.com, it may come via a number of networks and/or machines, and although we use our best endeavours to make sure that the data is not intercepted, we cannot guarantee that this will be the case. 

**Opting Out**  
From time to time, GamerWeb.com may offer its users the chance to receive information from GamerWeb.com or thirdparties, in services including, but not limited to, contests and promotions. You will always have the choice to opt out from such opportunities. If you do not opt out, you will always have the choice to opt out from whichever service you may have subscribed to, either by emailing the third party service you subscribed to, or by emailing info@gamerweb.com. 

**Further Policy**  
It is a GamerWeb.com policy that we will not disclose personally identifiable information you may choose to submit to GamerWeb.com to any third parties, unless otherwise stated for purposes including, but not limited to, the fulfilment of contests we may provide in association with thirdparties. In such instances, specific information regarding privacy and possible information disclosure will be provided. We follow a strict policy of no spam and no sales of personally identifiable information. 

**Cookies**  
Parts of GamerWeb.com use cookies to better provide our services and information. On the Internet, a "cookie" is file that a website transfers to a user's computer for record-keeping purposes. This is a common feature of many websites on the Internet, and is employed by GamerWeb.com to better serve to you our services and content. The file that is stored on your computer is small in size and does not identify you personally. 

**Advice**  
We recommend that you do not voluntarily disclose personal information in public areas of GamerWeb.com, although we do not prevent you from doing this. Public areas of GamerWeb.com include, but are not limited to, the GamerWeb.com Forums. We advise that all users of this service, and other public services at GamerWeb.com, use the service sensibly and with caution, as we cannot and will not be held responsible for the results of the disclosure of any information that may occur in these areas. 

**Children**  
Although the main demographic of GamerWeb.com does not encompass children below the age of thirteen (13), we welcome users of all ages to our content and services. If you are under the age of thirteen (13), we do, however, specifically request that you have the permission of your parents or legal guardian to view any content at GamerWeb.com and to take part in any and all services we offer, as we cannot and will not be held responsible for any information received or disclosed by our users. 

**Notes to Parents**  
We respect that you may wish to monitor the content and services your child uses on the Internet. If you wish for your child to be removed from any and/or all GamerWeb.com services, please send an email specifically requesting your wish to info@gamerweb.com. Please note, however, that while we will subsequently use our best endeavours to prevent your child from using our services, we cannot and will not be held responsible for access to our services your child may subsequently gain, as this is out of our control. 

**GAMERWEB.COM HUBSITES**  
At present, GamerWeb.com Hubsites are limited to: 

* SegaWeb.com ([http://www.segaweb.com](http://www.segaweb.com/))  

* SonyWeb.com ([http://www.sonyweb.com](http://www.sonyweb.com/))  

* NintendoWeb.com ([http://www.nintendoweb.com](http://www.nintendoweb.com/))  

* XboxWeb.com ([http://www.xboxweb.com](http://www.xboxweb.com/))  

* PC GamerWeb.com ([http://www.pcgamerweb.com](http://www.pcgamerweb.com/))

Please bear in mind these policies, and enjoy the content and services at GamerWeb.com! 

[[back to main page](http://www.gamerweb.com/)]
